The ones who changed will change everything.
The Darkest Minds is a action, adventure, drama
film directed by Jennifer Yuh Nelson.
After a disease kills 98% of America's children, the surviving 2%
develop superpowers and are placed in internment camps.
A 16-year-old girl escapes her camp and joins a group of
other teens on the run from the government.
Ruby Daly, played by Amandla Stenberg.
Liam Stewart, played by Harris Dickinson.
Clancy Gray, played by Patrick Gibson.
Charles 'Chubs' Meriwether, played by Skylan Brooks.
Cate Connor, played by Mandy Moore.
Suzume, played by Miya Cech.
The Darkest Minds is a 2018 American dystopian science fiction film directed by Jennifer
Yuh Nelson, written by Chad Hodge and produced by Shawn Levy and Dan Levine.
The film stars Amandla Stenberg, Harris Dickinson,
Mandy Moore and Gwendoline Christie.
Based on Alexandra Bracken's 2012 young adult novel of the same name, it follows a group of children who are
on the run from the government after obtaining superpowers due to a mysterious infection.
On September 15, 2014, it was announced that 20th Century Fox had bought the rights to the
novel and that Levy would produce the film through his 21 Laps Entertainment.
Stenberg was cast two years later on September 26, 2016, and principal
photography began in April 2017 in Atlanta, Georgia.
The Darkest Minds was released in the United States on August 3, 2018.
It received negative reviews from critics and was a box-office bomb.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book, dystopia,
super power, children on the run, woman director.
The tone is emotional.